http://www.torklift.com/privacy-policy

Support:
Towables
GlowStep Revolution Uprising (Doorway Mounted)
GlowStep Revolution (Mounted Beneath Doorway)
SafeStep
DirtDestroyer (GlowStep Series)
DirtDestroyer (Universal RV Step)
Towables
GlowStep Revolution Uprising (Doorway Mounted)
GlowStep Revolution (Mounted Beneath Doorway)
SafeStep
DirtDestroyer (GlowStep Series)
DirtDestroyer (Universal RV Step)
Towables
GlowStep Revolution Uprising (Doorway Mounted)
GlowStep Revolution (Mounted Beneath Doorway)
SafeStep
DirtDestroyer (GlowStep Series)
DirtDestroyer (Universal RV Step)
Back
Enter your zip/postal code or city and state/province to find a place near you:
Email
We here at Torklift International are committed to protecting the privacy of our website visitors and have enacted this privacy policy to better define to you our practices.
This policy covers torkliftcentral.com, but does NOT cover any third party sites we may link to that we have no control over.
This privacy policy sets out how Torklift International uses and protects any information that you give Torklift International when you use this website. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Torklift International may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
WHAT WE COLLECT
With your consent, we may collect the following information from orders, forms and surveys:
Your name
Contact information including email address
Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
We do NOT:
Share or disclose this information with other websites or companiesHave access to any information on your other browsing habits
Without your permission, we do NOT:
Collect personally identifiable information like your name, IP address or any other information that singles you out from our other users in an identifiably distinct manner without your explicit consent.
GOOGLE ANALYTICS ON OUR SITE
We utilize a tool known as Google Analaytics on our website to collect, compile and display anonymized, statistical information about our users to us to help better serve you.
We may look at the following information:
How long you stay on our site
Which pages you spend the most or least amount of time on
What type of computer, phone or tablet you're using
Other, related bits of data
WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
By using some of the data we collect, we're able to offer products that align with what you're looking for
Knowing what types of computers and screen sizes are visiting us allows us to develop pages that cater to you
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
This information provides invaluable insights to where we should grow, allowing us to bring you a better experience overall.
SECURITY
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
HOW WE USE COOKIES
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposesif you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at support@torklift.com.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to 322 Central Ave. N. Kent, WA 98032.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
We also utilize additional cookies furnished by Google Analytics. For an up to date list of these cookies and how they are used by the Google Analytics services, please view their documentation.
We are in strict compliance with Google Analytics Terms of Service.
